Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, but so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
So now tell me!
Where can I find Crocodile?
Luffy...
Luffy was right.
I've made up my mind now.
Change of plans.
We're going to go find Crocodile.
Yeah.
That does seem like the quickest way of
stopping the fighting from happening.
And we can quit wandering
around the desert, too.
That was beginning to get old.
So, where is he anyway?
This damn Crocodile guy? Let's see.
This is the capital city,
Alubarna, where my father rules.
And the rebel army is camped here,
getting ready to invade Alubarna.
So we just need to get to Crocodile
before the rebels can get to Alubarna.
This is where Crocodile is. Over here.
Rain Base.
Rain Base?
It's a city a bit to the north of
us, about a day's journey from here.
Okay,
did I or did I not tell the two of you to
quit with the pathetic
moaning all the time?
Who are you to talk?
You get to ride on the damn camel.
You could at least let us
ride Eyelash for a little bit.
You're a big fat camel hawk.
Get off your high horse.
Hey, Chopper, you've managed to
make it all day without collapsing.
Yeah, I'm trying hard not to.
Vivi, does this rain-based
city have a water supply?
Oh, yeah, no shortage there.
It's a gambling town, almost completely
isolated from all the fighting.
Ah! Gambling?
No way Nami, we're not
going there to gamble.
I guess people need some places
to relax, even here in Alabasta.
Come, come! No way!
Come on, give me some!
Come, come!
Leave me alone!
Come on, Lupe, just give
me one sip of it, please.
Isn't that why he gave it to us?
The old guy from the
sandstorm place gave it to me.
He had to dig all night
just to get this much of it.
We can't just go drinking it like it's
regular water or something, so no way!
Wow.
You can restrain yourself sometimes.
Well, yeah, of course I can, Nami.
That was a rude thing to say, you know.
Take another step. Hey, water.
So, how long till rain base, Vivi?
Hey, Luffy.
Thanks a lot.
I never would have been able to
make this decision on my own.
Okay, then give me food.
After I beat up Crocodile, give me food.
I'll eat till I explode.
I promise I will.
Please, Koza!
Just let me join you in the Rebels!
I will not.
And why not?
Don't I have every right to
be part of the rebellion, too?
I hate the king and the royal army.
Just let me fight with
you so I can prove it.
Barakla, show the kid.
He got that wound trying to protect
me in the middle of a battle.
Would you like to see the medical
tents and the grave sites, too?
It isn't pretty.
I'm not scared.
You can't scare me!
The cities have dried up
and a lot of people have
died because the king stole
all the rain from everyone.
My friends got sick because
there wasn't enough water!
It's all the King's fault!
I only want the chance!
Just let me fight!
I'm not scared of getting
injured or even dying!
That's where you're different from us
and why I can't let you join our ranks.
We're all afraid and
none of us want to fight.
Well, why do you fight then, Koza?
We don't do it because we want to.
We do it because we have to.
Because that's what our
country needs us to do.
Whether you understand that or not
makes little difference, so just leave.
Dammit, I told you to leave now.
Battle is no place for
a child, do you hear me?
What's wrong, huh?
It's not like you to rant and rave
like that, especially at a kid.
It was like looking at
myself when I was his age.
It made me angry.
And the worst part is I haven't
changed a bit since then.
Have we gathered all
the weapons we require?
No, it's proving quite difficult.
We need to begin contacting
all the other towns.
As soon as we have all the weapons,
we will begin our final
Alto attack on Alubarna.
Sire, it's only a matter of time now
before the rebel army attacks Alubarna.
We must take action against the
rebels quickly before it's too late.
I said no!
We'll not attack them!
This is not some little quarrel.
We strike first, they will strike back.
Sire, we are barely clinging
to power right now as it is.
That does not matter.
I don't care about my rule at the moment.
Ever since the Dance Powder incident,
it's been clear that someone's
trying to tear apart our country.
Are you suggesting that
we attack our citizens
before we determine who's behind all this?
Because that would be the true
destruction of our kingdom.
Don't you know?
A country is its people.
But sir, whoever is behind this
hasn't shown himself so far.
We can't sit back and wait for
this unknown force to divide us.
We must act. Can't you see?
Please understand.
I can't.
The king will not allow us
to take the offensive now.
We can barely even keep our own
soldiers happy at this point.
I would feel much better if we had
Igaram with us at a time like this.
Igaram has left a note saying that
he's leaving the island for a while.
Even as we speak, he and Princess
Vivi are still out there somewhere,
trying hard to figure
out who's behind this.
I hope they can.
Chaka! Pal! Come quickly!
What is it?
It's Karoo!
He's returned to the palace!
Karu's back?
We heard, Your Majesty.
Who sent that letter?
There's no mistaking it.
It's my Vivi's handwriting.
So, Your Majesty.
It means...
Karoo brought news from Vivi.
What does it say?
Father.
Everything I've written
here is true beyond a doubt.
Please read this letter carefully.
I've discovered the identity of the person
who's trying to destroy Alabasta Kingdom.
It is a warlord of the sea, Crocodile.
Because of Crocodile, Igaram is dead.
He died as he lived,
a hero to his country.
It's Crocodile.
I stupidly thought he was
loyal to the world government.
I never even wondered if he
was the one behind all of this.
How could he be dead?
He died as he would have wanted,
protecting Princess Vivi and Alabasta.
But now, Father, I have joined forces
with an amazing group of people.
They have given me great
confidence and power.
If I continue to work beside them,
I believe we will be able to make
a difference in this country.
We have reason to hope now.
Alabasta can and will be saved.
Please have faith, Father.
We can do this.
Vivi.
Vivi's letter mentions that you
fought very valiantly as well, Karoo.
You served her well.
Oh, it looks like you've been hurt.
Let me see.
Okay, no matter what happens
on that island, Remember,
this thing on all our arms
is a sign of our friendship!
Chaka!
We know the enemy's identity.
Prepare the soldiers to move out.
Phoebe's courage and Igaram's
death won't be in vain.
We're going to take action now.
We'll head for Rainbase and Crocodile.
Please do not be so hasty, Your Majesty.
Rainbase is far away and there
are many preparations to be made.
What's more, Crocodile has many of
the citizens firmly on his side.
even more of them than you do,
Sire, with all due respect.
If we send forces to
Rainbase now, your majesty,
the rebels will use our absence to attack?
and they will take the palace easily.
In which case...
It doesn't matter if the rebel army
destroys this palace completely.
It is only a building.
I've told you before, a
country is its people.
Even if our royal army does fall in the
end, if we can just defeat Crocodile?
this country can still be reborn as
long as its people are safe and whole.
If we battle the rebel army
instead, then that will all change.
In that situation, Crocodile's the victor.
Understand?
Majesty.
Yes, I see.
For right now, we do not need to
be focusing on the rebel army.
We just need to take out Crocodile.
This is one of the seven warlords
of the sea that we're fighting.
He is strong and cunning.
There will be many casualties, but we
must accept that and battle onward.
Chaka, we need to hold a war council.
Assemble the officers.
Pell, scout ahead and
conduct reconnaissance.
Right.
Forgive me for having
underestimated you, Your Majesty.
You are a true man of your country.
We head for battle tomorrow morning.
Sir, all soldiers are
to head for rain base.
There.
So is that the city?
That's it?
Are we here?
Crocodile.
Yeah!
Time to kick crocodile's ass!
That's rain base, huh?
So after all that's happened,
are we operating under the
assumption that Baroque
Works knows that we're here
on the island with them?
It seems likely.
We did run into Mr.
Two,
so I think it's safe to
assume that they have at
least some idea that we
were headed to Alabasta.
Who cares about that?
They know exactly what we look like,
so we won't be able to do much of
anything while we're in rain base.
Just lay low.
Then why is that?
Because if we get spotted
before we can find Crocodile,
I'm sure he can probably come up with all
sorts of nasty ways of taking care of us.
Assassination is kind of
their area of expertise.
Laying low, but we're coming, Crocodile!
You weren't even listening, were you?
Well, no matter what happens,
I will take it upon myself to
protect Nami and Vivi from any harm.
I'm always happy to play Prince Charming.
For a lady. Smooth one.
Smoother than you are, Zoro!
I need water.
There is none. Let it go.
Water... I'm going!
Wait for me, move me!
Hey, you might want to
take some money along.
Captain Smoker, why do you
think that they'll be here?
What reason would the Straw Hats
have for coming to Rain Base?
Let's just call it a hunch.
Yeah!
Finally we can get water!
I can't put my finger on
it, but something stinks.
I just feel like there's something
big lurking in the shadows.
Hey, old lady, give us some water, King!
Yeah, yeah!
A whole barrel!
No, we want more than that!
My barrel, yeah!
So then you really do believe that
there is some sort of a connection
between the Baroque Works Crime
Organization and the Straw Hats crew?
Water!
The only thing I know for sure is that
Straw Hat is out to get Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
This is about forever!
We need to hurry up and get
our marks on the others!
I'm going to go use the little boys' room.
Do you really think we can count
on them to stay out of trouble?
Even they can handle little errands, okay?
Right? I don't know.
I'll bet they managed
to screw something up.
It is Usopp and Luffy.
I'd start getting ready
to run if I were you.
Run away! Yeah!
Protect the water!
Right!
Dammit, we're going after them.
Get the marines to Shoujou. Sir!
Oh, right.
How much do I owe you?
If you know those brats, you'd better
add all the water they took to your tab.
Of course.
I'm so sorry.
What are the damn marines doing here?
How could I know that?
Let's just keep running for now!
You win.
Looks like the Marines are chasing them.
No way!
So why are those idiots running this way?
Hey, Tony hasn't made
his way back here yet.
He'll be fine.
Chopper can manage on his own.
Hey, you guys, I think the teams are here!
Hey, thank you!
We hadn't noticed that, Luffy!
Hurry it up!
We can't lose them this time, men!
Those idiots sure can run.
I'll give them that anyway.
This is bad!
Brokeworks will see us, if
we run through the city!
I think it's a little
too late for that, Usopp.
Then it's decided! Let's go! Huh?
Wherever Crocodile is,
how about it? Ready?
Do you see that building up ahead
with the alligator on its roof?
That's the casino that Crocodile runs!
It's called Rain Dinners!
I see it.
So that's where Crocodile is.
It'll be better if we all split up now.
Yeah, it's looking that way.
Right!
See you later!
Don't die! They split up!
Don't lose them!
Smokey! Hey!
You've got some real
nerve there, Straw Hat.
But don't think you can run forever!
White vine!
Ah, too close.
Damn.
Damn it.
Oh, no.
Look, over there.
It's them, all right.
No doubt. Kill them.
It looks like it's the
Baroque work's millions.
Well, then I guess we're stuck
between a rock and a hard place, huh?
Go on without me.
Hurry!
Okay.
Hey, Usak!
You look after Nami. Why?
Just do it.
I'll take care of the Marines.
Okay, I'm on it. But Sanji! Just go!
Without that smoke freak around,
they should be easy to handle.
Terribly sorry.
I hope Mr.
Bushido will be all right.
Is that all really pathetic?
Roronoa Zoro, I knew we'd meet again.
That voice.
I've been looking for you.
What do you think you're doing carelessly
cutting down civilians like that?
That's low even for you.
Look, I have my own reasons
for doing it, all right?
Besides, I have absolutely no desire
whatsoever to fight you again.
We settled our dispute fine in Longtown.
We did not.
I'm not through.
I haven't even dealt you a single blow.
Duh, she looked way too much like her!
And put that damn face
of yours away, will you?
What did you say?
You're insulting me?
That's a really pathetic tactic.
I'll make you pay!
Uh-uh, she's the one
person I can't handle!
Hold it!
Get back here, you rats!
It's two of them, all right.
We're...
we're okay!
Way to go, Usopp!
Look, up ahead!
It's the entrance to Rain Dinners!
And it looks like it's
in the middle of a lake!
What?
No one's here yet?
All right, let's get him!
Like fish in a barrel!
No, we're screwed!
It's Zoro!
Hold on, I thought Vivi was
supposed to be with you.
She was!
Are you saying she's not here?
Not yet, but maybe she
just went inside already.
Yeah, let's go in too.
Loopy!
Get back here!
It's that smoker guy.
Hey, you guys, let's go!
We have to run inside now!
Right behind you!
So he's in there!
Then I guess that's where I'm going!
Oh, Phoebe and the pirates
are in town paying us a visit.
Yes, we just received word from
the millions that they've arrived.
Let's be sure to welcome
them very warmly. Yes.
Listen up, crocodile!
I'm coming for you, and I'm
about to kick your sandy ass!
Get ready!